I just wanted to say, I know y'all don't see me, but I'm still here and I'm fortifying myself and
always paying attention to how I can be an educator and a change agent. But when you have
time to yourself, you are able to ruminate and consider and reflect. And I think one of the
interesting things that I have recognized in this recent back and forth is the failure to
understand the complexities that we have as humans and that we can be really, really great in some
areas and maybe have difficulty in other areas, et cetera. And I'm somebody who's always had
difficulty communicating one-on-one with certain people. Some people, it's no problem,
but I think because of the way that I speak, my tonality, my intensity, it can be misread
sometimes. I mean, sometimes I am being condescending, but oftentimes I'm not. Complaining is a word that's
applied sometimes to simply just being hyper aware of things and identifying it. And for anyone whose
feelings I've ever hurt, it was never intentional, I am definitely a constant work in progress in that
way. And I think sometimes we hold people in the public eye to a higher standard. And I know that as
a person in the public eye, I have to hold myself to a higher standard because of that. And we don't
necessarily get the same grace as if you have a frustrating interaction with somebody just at a
restaurant versus with somebody that you can name. But that's the reality of what happens when you are
in a public space as a performer, et cetera. And if you happen to be good at that shit, then that's how
you end up becoming a celebrity, which is really a term based on celebrated. That being said,
you know, I have seen, you know, the comments from people who say, you know, I had an interaction
with Amanda and I didn't, you know, feel good about it and et cetera. And just for what it's worth,
I care. I care about that. I know people are like, she don't give a fuck to it. I give so many fucks
because I don't ever want to be somebody who's in the world harming people. And I don't think
enough people acknowledge the way in which that they may harm me and how that can cause a reaction.
But I also acknowledge that sometimes my reaction possibly, actually could be incongruous to what
has been said to me. And that's my responsibility to take. And I take that responsibility. And I
understand how that can throw people off and misrepresent my character. And all I can do is,
you know, say that I'm constantly working on how to be better about managing that. That is the work
for me. I think that I'm somebody who really has taken a lot of time in my life, like as a late bloomer,
to really be able to understand the extra things that other people may need in terms of softness,
in terms of extra words, in terms of affirming, etc. And that's been like a big part of my
development. Because I think in my not I think I know in my younger years, that was something that
wasn't given to me. And so it's taken quite some examination and analysis and application and wax on
wax off to get better about, you know, giving it to others. In that I asked for grace. I asked for
understanding. And I want for myself the same that I want for everyone, which is community. And the
willingness to see beyond ourselves. I get mislabeled as egotistic all the time, simply because
I know what I'm talking about when I'm talking about it. But I want to be able to look at people
who are convicted of their vision and of their love for themselves as not egoism, but as a surety. And
let's build them up for that. We're in such a critical time, where so much of this time is about
how we love each other. And I have definitely been somebody who's had to learn different ways to love
because I wasn't loved in certain ways that I needed. And it takes time in our lives to learn
the things that we didn't even have access to. So I just wanted to say that and share that as I continue
to do my own self work and, you know, take some time away to really just get back to my own sense of
peace, etc. But just words to think on and to ponder and to consider. And I ask you the same
thing I ask myself when I get down and start beating myself up and start letting the outside words
convince me that I'm something I'm not. What are the things about you that bring something better to
this world? And how can you bring those things into the things about you that you feel may not?
For me, I am all about fairness. I'm incredibly fair person. I am all about justice. I am an incredibly
justice oriented person. And some of you might not think that but that's because you're basing your thoughts
on false information. I am 1000% about self actualization, about freedom, about liberation,
and about love, and about being able to see individuals in their own reflection, not in yours,
which is oftentimes I think one of the ways that we get tripped up. So I'll see y'all soon.